♪ Nipa hut, ♪
♪ even though it's small ♪
♪ The plants there ♪
♪ are all diverse. ♪
♪ Turnip and eggplant, ♪
♪ winged beans and peanuts! ♪
Hi!
My name is Aemie Romero.
Just a simple girl
studying at
Stonehurst University.
Taking up Bachelor
of Science in Biology.
I’m not just a regular
student, okay?
I’m also a university
scholar, yes!
I’m not just smart.
I’m beautiful,
and sexy too!
That’s according to my
mom, Mommy Alyana.
Of course, I got it from her.
I totally take after her.
And my simple life
suddenly changed,
because of something unexpected.
I met a man with a
strange personality.
And out of nowhere,
he suddenly said,
You're married to me now!
See?
Apparently, I’m already married?
From a college student and now,
a wife.
This man is so demanding.
Hey, woman!
You got a problem?
No, Dong.
But you know what?
Ever since we got married,
he’s been super sweet.
Hey, woman!
You talk too much!
Hurry up!
Wait, Dong.
I’m still telling my story here.
I have a secret to tell you.
But just between us, okay?
You know, I often
don’t understand him.
Because he seems...
a little dumb?!
Who are you talking to?
You look like an idiot!
See?
Now, I'm the idiot?
When he’s the real idiot!
Can't you make that
fucking speech faster?
See that?
How am I supposed
to make it faster?
Then you wouldn’t
understand me, right?
Besides, this isn’t
even a speech.
This is a prologue.
My husband is such an idiot.
Hey, woman! Who
are you talking to?
Hurry up!
We will be late!
Yes, hubby!
Coming!
He’s so sweet, right?
Alright, I have to go now.
He might get mad.
Wait, what is he again?
A driver?
A businessman?
A thief?
Oh my god!
My husband is a mafia boss!
We have different kinds of
drugs depending on their effects.
We have the
therapeutic drugs
for prevention,
diagnosis, and
treatment of diseases.
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
Prof. Lim's class is so boring.
Then...
we have illegal drugs.
The narcotics.
These are highly addictive,
and are being used and
sold by drug syndicates.
Illegal drugs?
Why is that the topic here?
Is Prof. Lim planning
to build a syndicate?
Oh no, then...
are we, her students,
going to become...
drug dealers?
Oh no, that’s not okay.
That’s not okay, I don’t
want my life to be ruined.
This is not okay.
Ms. Romero!
Do you agree with me?
No, ma’am.
I’m sorry, but I
don’t agree with you.
Then by all means,
if you have any ideas
on how to deal with it.
Deal with it?
Ma’am, no!
I will not allow you
to build a syndicate.
You’ll ruin our future, ma’am.
So no.
I will not allow it.
What are you talking
about, Ms. Romero?
You are our professor.
Please don’t lead us
down the wrong path.
Ms. Romero.
Get out...
of my class...
now.
Ma’am, ma’am.
If your salary as a
professor isn’t enough,
I can help you, ma’am.
There are other ways
to start over. I’ll help you, ma’am.
We can find a way.
Get out of my class now!
Aemie really has a
wild imagination, huh?
What do you think Aemie took?
Let me have some of that too!
All of you.
Don’t let your parents’
dreams for you be destroyed.
Don’t believe Prof. Lim.
I agree, I agree!
Shut up!
Or I'll fail all of you! Suck it!
You! Get out!
Cuz!
- Hey, cuz. You’re here early?
- Hi.
Don’t you have class?
That’s my cousin, Amesyl.
She lives with me
and Mommy Alyana.
Her parents already passed away.
We’re the only
family she has left.
Sad, right?
Yes, cuz.
Prof. Lim dismissed the class early.
Oh really?
Caileigh!
Hey, Caileigh.
- Hey, Caileigh.
- My god!
Why are you shouting? It’s like
you haven’t seen each other for ten years.
Aemie, I ran into Kevin
earlier, he’s looking for you.
And you too, Amesyl—
Louie’s looking for you.
You should’ve brought them here.
But wait, before
we change the topic.
You, Aemie—why are
you cutting classes?
What?
You’re cutting class, Aemie?
Right?
No, no, no, I’m
not cutting class.
Aemie, I know you.
And I know Prof. Lim.
She would never dismiss class early.
So why are you cutting classes?
I’m not cutting class!
Fine, if you won’t tell me,
I’ll tell Auntie.
Hey, no need to tell my mom.
Fine, fine, I’ll tell you.
OMG Ae!
You’re so silly, cuz!
Now even you guys
are laughing at me.
You’re so funny, Aemie.
[Aemie, you're being called
to Prof. Lim's office! Hehehe.]
Who’s that?
What is this?
I don't get it.
Yeah, that's terrible.
You read it.
Aemie, you’re being
called to Prof. Lim’s office.
That's what it says.
- Oh no!
- Oh no.
Why though?
Hey, what if she’s really forcing
me to become a drug dealer!
Oh please,
she’s just sending you
back to kindergarten.
Hurry up, or if
you take too long,
you might end up being sent to Aunt's womb.
You're in trouble.
Alright, let’s just meet
later at dismissal, okay?
- Alright, go.
- Alright.
Aemie, don’t let them send
you back to kindergarten!
Yes!
♪ A is for apple, ♪
♪ B is for ball, ♪
♪ C is for cat, ♪
♪ D is for dog... ♪
Why does my tone sound wrong?
No, no, no. That’s not it.
Think of something else.
♪ Nipa hut, ♪
♪ even though it's small. ♪
♪ The plants there ♪
♪ are all diverse. ♪
♪ Turnip and eggplant, ♪
♪ winged beans and peanuts! ♪
What comes after peanuts?
Oh no!
I can't go back to kindergarten.
I don't even know the basic
nursery rhymes!
I need to know them!
Or maybe...
I should just agree to become a
drug dealer.
That’s right, Aemie,
you’re so smart!
Go, fighting!
Fighting, Aemie, fighting!
Hi, ma’am. Hello.
I’ll get straight to the
point, Ms. Romero.
I did not like what
you did earlier.
- And because of that—
- Ma’am!
Ma’am, wait a second. Ma’am...
I don’t want— I don’t want to
go back to kindergarten, ma’am.
And if you’re sending me
back to my mother’s womb...
I won’t even fit in
there anymore, ma’am.
That would be very
inconsiderate of you, right?
I’m not trying to
assume anything.
But it kind of feels like
that’s where this is going.
If you really want me to
become a drug dealer...
That’s fine with me, ma’am.
I agree.
- I’m okay with it.
- What are you talking about, Ms. Romero?
Look at this.
Look at Prof. Lim.
Acting clueless now.
When she was just discussing
this in class earlier, right?
Because ma’am...
- Let me finish, Ms. Romero.
- Oh.
Sorry. Sorry, peace.
As I was saying.
I did not like what
you did earlier.
And if you ask me,
I would definitely fail you!
But after speaking
with the staff,
and even the
president of this beloved.
Stonehurst University,
you are still their top choice.
Because you still rank
first in all your exams.
Not just in my class,
but in all your subjects.
So we have decided that...
You’ll send me back to
grade school instead, ma’am?
Huh?!
Ma’am, thank you!
Thank you so much!
Ms. Romero!
- Sorry. Sorry, ma’am.
- My goodness!
Ma’am, maybe you can just send
me back to high school instead.
So I won’t have to go back to...
Wait, Ms. Romero!
Let me finish!
Okay, ma’am.
As I was saying.
We have decided
to make you the representative
of Stonehurst University
to convince Roswell Corporation
to invest in our university.
And that will also serve
as your punishment!
Oh, so ma’am, they...
Good luck, Ms. Romero!
Oh, just a bit of background.
It’s hard to convince the
owner of Roswell Corporation.
We’ve been trying
to get him to invest
for the past two years.
He really refuses to agree.
Prof. Lim must be out of her mind.
Even if I were Mr. Roswell,
I wouldn’t invest.
- Invest—
- Is there any problem, Ms. Romero?
Oh, none, ma’am. None at all.
What’s Mr. Roswell’s
full name again?
His name
is Ezekiel Roswell,
the CEO of Roswell Corporation.
Okay, ma’am.
OMG!
He's so handsome!
Very handsome!
Good morning, Mr. Roswell.
I need my full
schedule on Monday.
Uhm, meeting with Stonehurst
University's representative at 9 a.m.
Appointment with Mr. Chua at 10.
Lunch meeting with...
Cancel the first one.
But sir, that’s for a
possible partnership with...
You may go now.
Sir!
You heard me.
Come in.
Hi sir, here’s the
compilation of different women
and their personal backgrounds.
What time is it?
11:12, sir.
You’re fired.
- But sir, I was taking my—
- Leave!
They all look stupid.
Fiona, babe.
Let's talk about this.
Ezekiel, we're done.
This woman...
Yo! Zup, Moo?
What’s that?
Why are you researching about...
Your presentation is
on Monday, Ms. Romero.
You are not allowed
to tell anyone about this.
This is confidential.
Remember that.
Your full scholarship
depends on this, Ms. Romero.
Is that clear?
Right.
My scholarship depends on this.
If I lose it,
I won’t be able to finish college.
So I need to be careful
with my research.
Oh.
Moo, you’re here. Sorry.
Moo.
Hey, Moo.
Moo!
Why isn’t he answering me?
Wait...
Why does it feel
like he can’t see me?
What if...
while I was thinking
earlier, I suddenly fell
and then suddenly died?
Am I just a spirit now?
Hey, Moo!
Hey!
Can you see me?
Oh no, he really can't see me.
What if earlier...
a stray bullet
passed by and hit me?
Or maybe,
there was lightning and
it struck me?
Oh.
But it didn’t even rain.
Or maybe suddenly,
a storm came back and
I was the only one it hit?
I didn’t even get to say
goodbye to my loved ones!
But why...
why is there no white
light for me to follow?
Am I going to hell?
Moo?
Shit!
Why are you crying?
Moo?
You can see me now, Moo?
Yeah!
Are you dead too, Moo?
Huh?
Come on.
Let’s find the white light.
Let’s find the white light, Moo.
Wow, your imagination
really does go far, Moo.
That’s Nico Jeisz
Young. I call him MOO.
As in, My One and Only.
But hey, he’s not
my boyfriend, okay?
He’s just my boy best friend.
Hey it's Nico!
- You're right!
- Let's go say hi to him.
He's really handsome!
Hi, Nico!
In fact, you know what I think?
I think Moo is actually gay.
He just hasn’t come out yet.
I mean, that’s
totally fine, right?
No one should be
forced to come out.
Moo.
- I actually want to ask you something.
- Okay.
Do you already like someone
here in our university?
Huh?
You know?
You know already?
Just a little.
But...
Don’t deny it, Moo!
I already know your secret!
How did you find out?
See?
Confirmed!
I told you, he’s my sister!
Moo.
It doesn’t matter how I found out.
Just remember this, okay?
I accept you no
matter who you are.
Uhh, anyway
why were you researching
about methamphetamine earlier?
Huh?
What?
That’s just for
one of my subjects.
Subject?
Stop asking too many questions.
Because you’re not allowed to
know I’m researching illegal drugs!
Illegal drugs?
Why are you
researching illegal drugs?
Did I say illegal drugs?
Moo?
Are you hiding
something from me?
No, nothing.
Nothing, okay?
That’s so you,
Moo! Spill it already!
- I’m hungry, Moo.
- Ah.
I’m hungry. I’m heading home,
okay? Mommy might be looking for me.
Alright, I’ll see you.
Bye, Moo!
Excuse, excuse!
Hey, Aemie, where are you going?
I’m heading home.
- Going home already?
- Mhmm.
- By the way, say hi to Momo for me!
- Sure!
Take care!
- Bye, bye Aemie! Bye.
- Bye, boys!
Oh Nico.
When will you confess to Aemie?
Yeah, dude.
You're obviously
down bad for Aemie.
Hey, psst.
Let's eat.
- Oh yeah. Let’s go, let’s go.
- Let’s go.
- We still have class later.
- You're staring too hard.
Let’s go, let’s go.
Here.
Thanks.
Oh, auntie.
Let me help you.
Oh.
Amesyl!
Where’s...
Baby Ae, you’re not with her?
Auntie, Aemie...
OMG!
Huh?!
Baby Ae!
What happened to her?
Auntie.
She left us!
Where did I go wrong?
Auntie, Auntie!
Okay, here we go.
I did everything, Amesyl.
I worked so hard.
For the two of you.
- Okay, Auntie.
- Why?!
What am I still lacking?
Mommy, I’m here!
Baby! Baby Ae!
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Amesyl, call an ambulance!
Huh? An ambulance, really?
Yes, so we can bring
her to the hospital.
- Are you okay?
- I’m okay, Mommy.
You don’t have amnesia, right?
Huh? Do you recognize me?
I’m your mommy.
Your mommy!
- I’m your mommy!
- Mommy!
Mommy, I’m okay.
Why did you run away?
Mommy, I just finished
a presentation for school.
You ran away because
of a presentation?
No, Mommy.
It’s on Monday.
On Monday?
Did you hear that?
Your cousin will
leave us on Monday!
What kind of
presentation is that?
Mommy, Mommy, calm down.
It’s like this, Mommy.
What I mean is,
the reason I got home late
is because I finished my
presentation for Monday.
What kind of
presentation is that?
Is it singing?
Like...
Or I can help you with that.
Or maybe dancing?
Oh lord.
Yeah, you know, I’m the queen of...
Queen of...
Anyway, I’m the queen!
I’m the queen!
Mommy, it’s just a big
presentation I have on Monday.
You can definitely do it.
Just do your research and be prepared.
I’ll help you.
But,
help me finish this first...
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh my, this is crazy.
- Miss!
- You can do it, Baby Ae!
I’m on my way to Roswell Corp.
To scout and prepare
for my meeting.
Is this Roswell Corp.?
It’s huge?!
I wonder what Mr. Ezekiel
Roswell looks like.
Oh, never mind.
Ezekiel Roswell...
Oh?!
He’s such a private person.
I guess...
he’s bald...
and ugly, this
Mr. Ezekiel Roswell, right?
Come on, come with me.
This is it!
Oh miss, miss, miss.
Wait.
Do you have a pass?
Pass?
- Pass?
- Yes, a pass.
For this building.
So you can enter.
Pass?
Why are they asking
me for a password here?
For social media?
AemieDollie143.
Wait, let me check.
Ah, ma’am.
I think what you said is wrong.
Wrong?
Why is it wrong?
That’s the password I use
for all my social media.
Ah, sir. Do it like this.
Aemiedollie143.
All lowercase.
That’s final.
Ma’am, it’s still not there.
If you don’t have a pass,
you’re not allowed to enter!
Am I really going home in tears?
What could my password be?
Why is it wrong?
I'm starving.
Where should I eat?
Is this the end for me?
Aren’t I the main character here?
Am I really dying in episode 1?
Oh well,
I guess that’s just how life is.
Goodbye, guys!
What the fuck are
you doing, miss?
Am I already in heaven?
But why is the angel swearing?
Miss.
Open your eyes.
Can’t you fucking hear me?
This angel is so handsome!
Wow!
Can you take me
after Monday instead?
I still have a
presentation. It’s important.
And I also want to
make up with Dollie first
before you take me to heaven.
Are you insane?
I knew it.
I’m still alive! Thank you, Lord.
I knew it, I’m alive!
Get in.
Me?
Kid.
Your father said to get in!
Huh?
I don’t have...
You think you don’t!
But you do!
You do! You do!
Don’t be mad at
your father anymore!
Please!
Can’t you see yourself?
You’re so dirty already!
I know you’re starving.
You’re not eating
properly anymore.
You’re just wandering
around the streets!
Look at you, you can’t even eat!
So please!
That’s enough, go
back to your father!
Oh!
My bad.
My bad, kid. Sorry.
Alright, go now.
Miss, can I ask for
money to buy food?
My siblings and I
haven’t eaten yet.
Okay, wait a second.
Here, take all of this.
Take it, all of it.
Thank you!
What am I going to do now?!
How am I going to get home?
What if I call my cuz?
She can’t find out about the meeting.
Hey, woman.
I said, hop in!
Oh, okay.
What the fuck?
What are you doing?
You said, "hop in". So I did.
In the car!
Idiot!
Who are you calling an idiot?!
- Hey, how do I start this?
- Get out.
You told me to get in earlier!
Now that I did, you’re
telling me to get out.
I’ll be driving!
Move!
Why did you give me a ride anyway?
Where are we going?
I’ll take you to the hospital.
Why are we going
to the hospital?
I’m not sick.
Is he really not going to talk?
What a waste, I’m such
a fun person to talk to.
Oh, I know, I know.
I’ll just ask questions instead.
What’s your name, by the way?
Hello!
Can you hear me?
My favorite color is pink.
By the way, I’m Aemie Romero.
You can call me Ae for short.
So it’s easier for you.
My favorite number on
the electric fan is number 2.
Do you like Dollie too?
My dream travel destination
is the Bermuda Triangle.
You?
Still nothing.
Do you know why I’m here?
Because my professor
keeps forcing me to sell drugs.
Drugs?
There!
So you can talk after all!
So drugs are what make you talk.
Yes, drugs.
Then I’m going to,
I’m going to present
at Roswell Company
on behalf of
Stonehurst University.
Stonehurst University?
Yes.
Do you know the
CEO, Ezekiel Roswell?
You know how I imagined him?
Short, bald,
wrinkly skin—in short, ugly!
Ouch!
Why did you suddenly brake?!
Out!
Out?
I said, out!
Shouldn’t it be “ouch”?
Tchh, tch, chh.
Can’t you say “tch”?
You should have just said, "Ow."
Get the fuck out!
Hey, I don’t want to!
You let me ride in here,
then you’re just
going to kick me out.
I said get out!
I can’t, I can’t get out.
I already gave all my
money to that kid earlier.
Because I thought
he was your child.
And also,
I don’t even know where we are.
One, two, three, four, five
six, seven, eight, nine...
ten thousand?
What am I supposed to
do with your ten thousand?
Don’t tell me that’s
still not enough.
Just give me a map instead.
Because I won’t be able to get
home. I’ll get lost without a map.
Give it to me.
I need a map!
I badly need a map!
Hey.
O-M-G!
You work here at Roswell?
Follow me.
Wow!
Hey, hey!
You didn’t tell me?!
You’re a driver here.
Wait.
Good morning, sir.
So, this is how it is in Roswell.
They call drivers, "sir".
Uh, miss.
You’re not allowed to
enter without a pass.
You really don't listen.
Sir, I’m with him.
That driver over there.
Huh?
What driver?
Don’t try to fool me.
You’re not allowed inside.
Hey, woman.
Didn’t I tell you to follow me?
Aren’t you going to stand up?
Sir, if you’re going to rob
me, I don’t have any money.
Look at this guy.
It feels like he has bad
intentions toward me.
Stand up, I said!
Sir, please don’t.
Please, sir, don’t.
Look at me.
No, sir, please! Don’t.
Look at me!
Oh!
It’s you.
Sorry, it’s you.
I thought it was someone else.
I told you to follow me.
Well, they wouldn’t let me in.
They said the password
I gave was wrong.
What?
Who?
Who wouldn’t let you in?
You.
I don’t want to see
your face anymore.
Sir, please don’t fire me.
My children are
still young, sir!
Hey, sir.
Don’t be sad, sir.
It’s okay.
Oh, I have an idea.
When the driver passes by,
just hide.
But ma’am, he said
I’m fired, ma’am.
No!
You’re not fired!
He didn’t say you’re fired.
He just said he
doesn’t want to see you.
So when he passes by again...
There, there, there,
there—hide there,
under the table.
I told you to follow me.
Okay!
Sir, do that, okay?
Yes, ma’am. Thank you, ma’am.
- Bye!
- Thank you!
Good morning, sir.
They all call you "sir"?
Why?
Are you the boss
of the drivers here?
Head driver?
Oh my God!
I get it now.
What?
That’s why they respect you so much.
Because...
You’re Mr. Ezekiel Roswell’s driver?
Amazing!
Wow!
It’s huge!
It’s even bigger than our house.
So Mr. Roswell is an engineer too.
What are you doing?
Why are you stealing?
That’s bad!
Psst hey. Stop that, I
don’t want to go to jail.
I still have so much...
Shut up.
You wear this.
What am I supposed
to do with this, sell it?
Idiot!
You’re not selling it.
Pawn it?
At what pawnshop?
It’s yours.
You’re so dumb.
You keep calling me dumb.
You’ve said it way too
many times already.
Wait here.
Why did he give me a ring?
It’s not even my birthday.
What’s the occasion today?
Ouch.
Ah, it’s real. It’s real.
That hurts.
- That means—
- No way!
- That happened earlier!
- This...
- Looks good! I promise.
- I can't find you.
Are you the principal here?
Hey, you crazies!
Hey!
Hi, Momo!
Where’s Moo?
Wow. Is my cousin really
the only thing in your head?
But you haven't
said anything to her.
- What. What’s going on?
- It’s obvious.
What?
Another girl again...
Another girl?
Wow, unbelievable!
I'm loyal to Shan.
- Oh, right.
- As you should, dude.
She’s my twin,
you should be loyal.
And she’s arriving soon.
Really?
By the way. Have
you guys seen Aemie?
Should we call her?
Yeah, let’s do that.
You!
- Call her.
- Why don’t you call her?
- You were the one who thought of it.
- You do it. She’s your cousin.
Uhh, come on, Amesyl.
Fine. What am I
even going to say?
What if.
You confess
- that you love my cuz so much.
- There!
- Go on, go on.
- So arrogant!
Alright, fine, I’ll call her now.
That’s why we’re friends!
There.
Wait.
Hello, cuz?
Hi, cuz!
Hi, Aemie!
Oh, you’re all together?
Is Moo there?
Are they with you, cuz?
That's me, that's me!
Ask anything.
- Anything.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- Anything?
- Yes, anything.
Come on!
Cuz.
Do you know...
Magellan?
No. What course is he in?
- Oh, you’re so dumb.
- She thought he's our classmate.
Why are you laughing?
Is Magellan your boyfriend?
You’re so stupid!
Magellan!
The one Lapu-Lapu killed, right?
Oh yeah.
Hey.
But cuz, that’s bad, right?
Mommy said it’s wrong
to accuse someone, right?
Who are you talking to?
Huh?
Cuz, who’s that?
Are you with a guy?
Huh?
Uhh.
It’s...
it’s Zeke.
Zeke.
Zeke?
- I don’t know any Zeke.
- Who’s Zeke?
Cuz!
Zeke is the driver...
Huh?
Hung up?
Damn it, she hung up on me.
- Zeke?
- Hey, maybe she’s hiding something.
- I don’t know any Zeke from Stonehurst.
- Oh my.
- This girl is crazy.
I said, who are you talking to?
Why did you take my phone?
I told you to wear the ring.
Okay.
Fine.
It looks nice on me...
Come in.
Hi, sir.
Here’s the food you ordered.
Okay.
Where is that woman?
Which woman, sir?
Aemie.
Where the hell are you?
What the fuck are
you doing there?
There’s...
there’s a cockroach.
I wanted to make it a pet.
A cockroach as a pet?
Why?
I just want to.
You’re such a buzzkill.
Hello.
Can you just eat?
I know you’re hungry.
Go on.
Why does she have a ring?
You may leave now, Kate.
Okay, sir.
Who was that?
Is that your boss?
Why...
did she look at me like that?
Huh?
Oh my God!
Was that Mr. Roswell?
Mr. Roswell is a woman?
What are you talking about?
He’s not Mr. Roswell.
Oh.
Oh, so Mr. Roswell is a man.
Hey!
Hey, Zeke!
Do you have a relationship
with Mr. Roswell?
That’s okay!
Love wins!
What the fuck?!
I’m not gay!
Can you just eat?
Hey!
Thank you!
I knew it,
you’re thoughtful
even if you’re cold.
Thank you.
But...
who really is Mr. Roswell?
It’s for you to find out.
Find?
Why?
Is Mr. Roswell missing?
Zeke!
Zeke, that can’t happen!
If he disappears,
Stonehurst will lose its investor,
and I’ll lose my scholarship!
Can you just shut up!
Because, Zeke, my...
my meeting this Monday.
It has to push through.
Please, you have to help me.
Please.
Your meeting on
Monday will push through.
I’ll handle it.
Really?
Promise?
Yes.
Thank you!
Thank you, Zeke! Thank you...
Just eat.
Okay, thank you!
You don’t want any?
I don’t.
Are you sure?
I’ll finish all of this. You
really don’t want any?
I said I don’t!
Okay.
This is so good!
You really don’t want any?
Are you sure you’ll take me home?
Won’t your boss get mad?
He might look for you.
It’s already late.
I have to bring you home.
What am I going to tell Mommy?
I’m dead.
I’m sure she’ll get mad.
But it’s okay.
This is for
Stonehurst University.
And besides, right, Zeke?
You promised me,
you’ll help me convince Mr. Roswell.
Why do you...
want Mr. Roswell
to invest in
Stonehurst University?
Well, you know, right?
My scholarship depends on it.
If he doesn’t invest,
I’ll lose my scholarship.
If that happens,
how will I get a good job?
And also...
What if Mommy, cuz,
and I end up struggling?
How will I give
them a good life?
Right?
What if he doesn’t agree?
Hey!
Hey, Zeke!
Don’t be like that.
You said you’d help
me convince him, right?
And Zeke, I believe you’re kind.
Because earlier, you gave me food.
Then you gave me a ring.
And now you’re taking me home.
So I believe you’ll help me.
You talk too much, you know?
There, there. Turn there.
That's the way home.
Too bad, auntie,
we didn't sell much.
Miss, do you still
have two pieces left?
- Oh no, we’re closed already.
- That’s too bad.
Oh, okay. Thank you.
Oh, boy.
Can't he see we're already
packing up?
Let's hurry so we can go inside already.
Oh, so he is a gentleman.
Oh.
Oh, she’s good, very good.
No, stay there. Put that down.
Aemie Romero.
Who is that man and why
are you only getting home now?
Hi, Miss.
Are you Aemie Romero?
Because I’m asking Aemie Romero.
So if you’re not Aemie
Romero, can you not interrupt?
Cuz. This is Zeke.
Zeke, this is my
cousin and my mommy.
Baby Ae, why are you late?
Where did you go?
Who is he?
Your suitor?
Your boyfriend?
- Why don’t you let him come inside?
- What?!
No, Mommy.
He’s not my boyfriend.
That’s embarrassing, Mommy!
This is Zeke.
Hi, ma’am.
Hi, Zeke. I’m Alyana.
I’m Zeke.
- Come inside first.
- Oh.
Oh no, Auntie, he has
somewhere to go.
Right?
You have somewhere to go?
Niecy, let him stay first. Right?
Auntie!
She’s right, madam.
I’m afraid I have to go.
Oh, he’s leaving.
Alright, you can go.
That’s too bad.
But I’m sure you’ll come back, right?
I’ll be back for sure.
Okay.
Aemie.
Zeke.
I’ll see you at the meeting.
Okay.
Bye!
I’ve got this, I’ve
got everything.
I’ll take care of it,
I’ll clean all of that.
Hello.
Hello, sir.
Don’t cancel my meeting
with Stonehurst
University on Monday.
Oh, okay sir.
And please tell them to make sure
that a certain Aemie Romero
will represent the University.
Or else I won’t be there.
Okay?
Okay, sir.
Miss Romero,
may I see your speech and
presentation for later?
Do I need an opening speech
when pushing drugs?
Talking in front of
the panel is no joke, okay?
Especially, if Mr. Roswell is there.
Is that Zeke?
Zeke!
I just wanted to thank you
because I feel like
you're the reason Mr. Roswell agreed
to meet up with me.
What did you prepare for the meeting?
Prepare what?
What's this?
Before we begin,
party hats for everyone.
I already signed the contract.
It's your dad's last will and
testament that before you
inherit his riches,
you need to get married.
I found a wife already.
That's an engagement ring, right?
Right?
Oh my God!
Oh my God, it is!
Why do I feel nervous?
Oh, no. My heart
is beating so fast.
Hey, Zeke!
Ah!
What?
Say, ah!
Well, I'm glad to finally meet
the woman Mr. Roswell's marrying.
Huh?
Mr. Roswell's getting married?
Certificate of Marriage?